DAFFA RAYHAN MAHARDHIKA

Depok, West Java | 082211359531 | daffarayhan18@gmail.com | daffarayhan.netlify.app

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Technological advances are accelerating. It is making me want to become an expert Developer and deepen JavaScript progress. Finally, I have been following the intensive program for 2 months at PT Code Development Indonesia. The bootcamp gives me a comprehensive view of what I can do as a JavaScript Programmer.

EDUCATION

STATE POLYTECHNIC OF JAKARTA

Jakarta, ID

Associate Degree of Engineering

Major in Electrical Engineering

Okt 2020

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Proficient in JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML/CSS, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Frameworks: React.js, React Native, Vue.js, Node.js, Next.js

Developer Tools: React Hook, React-Redux, React Context, Axios, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Vuetify, Ant Design, Git, Jira.

Relevant Skills: Web Performance, Clean Code, REST API, Graphql, UI Design, Material UI.

Course & Training:

- React and Node Bootcamp Full Stack Node JS Code.id.
- Frontend Developer (React) HackerRank
- JavaScript (Basic) HackerRank
- CSS (Basic) HackerRank

EXPERIENCE

PT. Cudo Communication

Tangerang, ID

Frontend Developer

April 2024 - Present

Freelance Web Developer

Jakarta, ID

Frontend Developer

Jan 2024 – March 2024

PT. Code Development Indonesia

Jakarta, ID

Software Developer

May 2021 - Dec 2023

PROJECTS

Visitor Management System - Website

Dec 2024 - Present

- Developed an interactive dashboard to display real-time visitor logs. Features include search, filtering, check-in/out status, and data visualization with charts. Implemented Face QR for seamless visitor check-in and check-out using facial recognition and QR codes. Integrated with a backend API for efficient visitor data management.
- Build a front-end application using Next.js
- Technical Stack: TypeScript, Next JS, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, ECharts.

Coverage and Ondesk Tools (Lintas Arta) - Website

Sept 2024 - Present

- Developed a dynamic web application enabling users to upload and manage Excel data with advanced features like in-place editing, sorting, and filtering using React Grid. Integrated an interactive coverage map to visually display locations and a chart feature within the table to show the status of each file (In Progress, Completed).
- Build a front-end application using Next JS
- Technical Stack: TypeScript, Next JS, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, React Grid, ECharts

Fleet Management System (MBG) - Website

Aug 2024 - Present

- Developed a fleet management dashboard system for assigning tasks to drivers, monitoring their real-time locations and data charts for visualizing and analyzing key metrics such as driver productivity and fleet usage.
- Build a front-end application using Next JS
- Technical Stack: TypeScript, React, Next JS, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, ECharts.

Employee Management Dashboard (BNPB) - Website

April 2024 - July 2024

- The Employee Management Dashboard was built to streamline the management of employee-related data, enabling administrators and HR staff to monitor employee details, attendance, performance, and other key metrics in real time.
- Build a front-end application using React
- Technical Stack: JavaScript, React, React Redux, Material UI.

Chica Dashboard - Website

Jan 2024 – March 2024

- A freelancer project that develops a website dashboard and implement static to dynamic token
- Build a front-end application using React
- Technical Stack: TypeScript, React, React Redux, Tailwind CSS, Jira.

Astraotoshop - Mobile

Feb 2023 - Dec 2023

- Develop a marketplace for vehicle spare parts products company (Astra Otoparts).
- Build a front-end application for android using React Native.
- Technical Stack: JavaScript, React Native, React Redux.

Astraotoshop - Website

June 2022 – Jan 2023

- Develop a website admin and customer for a marketplace vehicle spare parts products company (Astra Otoparts).
- Build a front-end application using React.js.
- Technical Stack: JavaScript, React.js, React Redux, Ant Design

Fastana Logistic - Website

May 2021 - May 2022

- Develop a logistic management system for a global supplier of transport and logistic company (Fastana Logistic).
- Build a front-end application using Vue.js.
- Technical Stack: JavaScript, Vue.js, Vuetify.

M-Cash Logistic - Website

May 2021 - July 2021

- Develop a logistic management system for a global supplier of transport and logistic company (M-Cash Logistic).
- Build a front-end application using Vue.js.
- Technical Stack: JavaScript, Vue.js, Vuetify.